Sam's on the horizon
In episode 1 of Chinese School
China Holmes a 250 million scooter
Children 450,000 primary schools 235 languages and the small town
Auctioning
Story of three schools here over the year of the golden pig
Jordan is home to just 50,000 people
Tiny by Chinese standards it lies in the rural province of anway
450 kilometers from Shanghai
Even here in shielding the pace of changes first new windows meeting at
Proud of two very different things and teaching
Will's father life
At 3 Ashi owning schools high school
House for Scholars
Which is a little less pressure
And pigment primary
A new charity from school 3 schools
In one time in a small coronavirus China
Tangela
Journeyman
And these children are preparing to face a challenge that will change their lives forever
Bowling.com
Mr. who the Headmaster of shooting High School
Remind students of the odds stacked against them
Limoncello
Cheerleading High School is the top school in town
I'm one of the best in older than weigh
A promise of more than 80 million people
The children at the school range from 16 to 18
Every one of them has excelled all the way through the Chinese education system
And as of the 2000 children's at the school one of the most promising
A seventeen-year-old will you play
More than 10 million students will sit the gaokao
The university entrance exam
Will you face close to civista her expects her lost love her
Mexican buffets
The best student in the school
Old school
Hope that you can school verify I mean the Kaboom preschool in
But right now
Will you say until friends have other things on their minds
Play music
Will you face mother is doing everything she can to maximize her daughter's chances of success
Like almost every school pupil in China
Do you say is an only child
Everyday
Two meals and bring them to her daughter
W fatal do the moment to study time
Cousin
Bosa
Yeah
$5 championship
Prodigy
Where's Johnny want to how they're trying to ask for your thoughts mean
Am I awake it's the Stars
Another day at the towns father Secondary School
Taking children from 12 to 18
But you didn't say I do sit major exams when they're 16
The brightest and who could transfer at Union High School for a better chance of going on for top university
It's 11:30
But instead of going to the canteen to eat with his friends
Sixteen-year-old lyrics Young
Is taking a working lunch
Exams in 4 weeks
Every spare minute to spell revising
Because he set his heart on getting into the high school
Younger
Toledo Zoo
Washington
Mega Machamp
But it sounds interesting
Love's Chinese pop music
And his dad's taxi even though he come drive
You Shanks desperate to get behind the wheel
T-Mobile Lincoln Ave
Enchanting town
Dooney greeted with exercises practice this way for over a thousand years
I'm some newer ones too
But today is no ordinary day
Chinese families get together
Celebrate Ching Ming
The grave sweeping Festival is a time for people to visit family Graves
Offer up prayers
I'm pay respects to that ancestors
Today musician will try to stop worrying about the
Future
And instead focus on the bus
Family stuck off of incense
Fireworks and he'll money
Replica banknotes
Band give the ancestors some spare cash in the afterlife
Randleman
Saw movie music
Cost of the Zumba
I'm communication
Sometimes means asking for a little extra help
Susana Mendoza
Will you be a couple Savannah
The whole family is that
Including grandma live
Beyonce Savage
Mojang
Fishes
Suzuki
The youngest singer
He hasn't stopped.
The final year students at Sheldon High School
Everything is focused on the exams
Today
Top students will you stay until closer at the local hospital
For the compulsory pre-exam checkup
Every time a student is tested to ensure that healthy enough to take University entrance exam
The test can affect the whole future
Light City costume
So who your face it's a real chump to put down her books
Elsa
The range of tests are designed to make sure that they're in perfect working order for University
Nusensei left unchecked
Bill of health
They cannot focus on the real challenge ahead
Play something
Everyday at shooting High School
Is a test of fitness and endurance
Crossing at 5:45 a.m.
6 a.m. for 45 minutes of self-study
Reading aloud is the preferred way to learn subject by heart
Octopus
Does 30 minutes about Robux exercise
Uber for breakfast
Xtend Barre
To the classroom
Well Essence run until 11:30
Najma shirokiya
I'm classes start again with 15 minutes at I exercises
Which chamomile believed helps to improve eyesight
Listen to continue until 5
Then out to dinner it back in the classroom at 7 p.m. formal study
From Monday to Saturday class and every night at 10:15
At 10:30
Teachers panda costumes of any students who might still be trying to study
Most children had to
But final-year pupils like move you say
Still have hours of work to go
Like many other exam yes Jesus
He went to the room of Campus so she can carry on working when the classroom lights have been switched off
Every night
Will you face mother leave the family home 10 minutes away
To say the night with her daughter
At 12:30 another average day for will you say comes to an end
It's 6 a.m. at Pigman Primary School
On the outskirts of Sion in town and close to the famous yellow mountains
It was Ruth's children from all over the county
Every tiny child is supposed to have nine years of formal education
Three children
Bingman school is that first step on the Long March to University
The school's headmistress
Is mrs. John
Under highwatch relia 60 children ranging between the ages of 7 and 12
Awesome awesome
Beehive
One of the growing number in China
Games to teach abroad a curriculum the most only Chinese food
Go Panthers
Donegal a shisha. Watches
Bottom of panties
You'll
Primary school is free in China
But many parents still have to pay for books and other school expenses
Demons boarding school
But because it's run by a charity all food clothing and school books are provided free
The children come from pool families who couldn't afford these extras themselves
This is John Ping
She's 10 years old and has been at the school for two years she likes picking tea with her dad
Making things
Anthony
But more than anything else
She loves Escape
Today is a big day for dumping
Because mrs. John has also to be a special helper in class
Show me acting in a play
Designed to teach the pupils to take care of that possessions
Episodes of time
The school provides each of them with our own pencil and eraser
But one of the children haven't treated as well
I just about to beat with a lesson
Chinese-style
Team
FedEx
Mase rapper
Demon
Pasadena
Hi aana
Call.
Dunking in the other class monitors
Look for the best-kept examples
Hi Google.
Protestantism
The cost and votes on the most by soda razor
Amazing
Call.
It's seven-year-old when hung Chan
How
Bloomington
Play Eazy-E
Call Candy
What was
Fremont
Thunderstorm
Ha ha
Shut up
What does
Cookie unpleasable
Godzilla costume
Dollar Tree
Hoverboards
As a sign of forgiveness
Wyndham changma shake hands with every one of his classmates and recite the promise song
Gaga
Coyote
Great
Haha
Magnesium
Indiana images
Who do I stay with
Asia
All Is Forgiven and forgotten
The children head out to the organic vegetable patch
Certain eyes from the school's latrines
When home Chang seems to have recovered from his adolescent
Bedtime
Loudoun girl
Omaha
Toyota parts
Hey Auntie
What's the primary school children do physical labor in the fields
Go to high school students are doing exercises of an entirely different kind
The final year students in mainstream Secondary School
Take an academic exam to get into University
But there's also an option to major in sports
On top of the academic exam
These students have to do a practical Athletics test
Which accounts for 50% of the final mock
Mr. Wanda PE teacher
Was himself a student at Union High School
Now he's preparing his students for that greatest challenge
Send it
Videos
Chico
Listen to the children
Mr. Wang's top sports teams
A seventeen-year-old who kite
He's in his final year at Union High School do the training means he works have a fearsome appetite
His favorite stuff
Kukai studies 10 hours a day
I'm trying another 3 hours daily for his Sports exams
Limoncello
The toy kashamu
Tucson
Spiritual that you hot
At issue are you
Selena woman Sinatra
The school students have their own way of bringing themselves good luck
Stony imagines
She want
Wheeling Tire
Does an added incentive to do well
Because mr. wine has threatened his little pigs if they don't succeed
Hatzolah YouTube
But despite Mr wines toughness fukai looks up to
Please
Tomorrow I will travel 200 miles to underway teacher training University
To compete in the exam he spent the last two years working for
Zion Middle School
Luciana discuss makes her a chance to unwind
They've been working hard for exams
So that teachers have organized a day out
Why do you cry
What's the pop music song duji on gets the singing going
No he's got competition
Molding Bowser
25 minutes from the yellow mountains are one of China's most popular pilgrimage enterocytes
To celebrate three years across makes the children have built themselves a birthday cake
As usual
Lucian lead the singing
What zone is about
Song Thai song
But despite the High Spirits
It's hard to forget that the monks and next week
Is Alfredo Villa
But this ancient wisdom of his little Comfort solution
Indian Trail
Doesn't want anything
Call
Some of the children the trip has been a relaxing break
But not everyone can sleep
What do you want
Primary School
That halfway through the summertime
10 year old campaign has worked really hard
Ikea
Danielle
Hey you and yeah
CityView
Imogene
Magazines
It's just a 2-mile bus ride away
A trip to Sion in town is a big deal for come2go like camping
With a population of just 50,000
Germantown howdy registers on the map of China but it's changing Falls
Hunting the world away from the Tranquility of Pigman School
Message Hazel Honda
Faisal Haider
Michael Hogan
I don't either
Pizzaland
Can I come
Life at Pikmin seems good for camping
But her grandmother knows it was very different just two years ago
Sahara
So
Trillionaire
Padme Amidala
U-Haul
Nearly a quarter of adults have left Android Province to find jobs elsewhere
Making the traditional family unit lesson less common
Dumb things home is with her grandparents in a remote to producing Village
As Farmers they always struggle to pay school fees
So when Pikmin offered have a scholarship
It seems the chance of a better life
She's doing
How many people watch water company
Hiya hiya
You can use a Cutlass
You can use a condom
Come here
Jessica
Cinderella.
Special
The Hildebrand way maybe beautiful
But many of their inhabitants of particularly pool
Every year head mistress misses John has deep into the mountains to find scholarship candidates for payments who
The stuff is that
Tiny Hamlet of shutting
They have an appointment at the home of six-year-old Chen Wei ping
Synagogue
Young Thug
Manila
Does Epsom salt
Banana ketchup
Vanessa.
How the food chain
You think
Junior
Sunny mama
Finding my
Not The Descendants as anymore
Last year at ny-penn was abandoned by his mother
Leaving his grandparents to look out for him
Real American
He's an ideal candidate for the school
But with his mother gone they count immediately alfano place
Because she still his legal guardian
This is Gianna hatim head off on the three-hour journey to see that next hopeful family
Syllogism
Citizenship
Chattanooga
Fujifilm camera
Virginia Plan photo
The teachers have reached that decision
Superman
Nothing
Omaha
Pop sprocket
Although it means leaving her father behind
It's a great opportunity for chatting leeway made to start a new life
Play teacher training Stadium
Kukai on 10,000 other competitors
Places at University
Temperatures exceed 75 degrees
Bouquets performance is not living up to expectations
The shot put the 100 in the 400m bubblegum badly
Ukiah schools that has lost and toughest race
The 800m
It's his final chance to rescue his school
Gojira
Tuba
Running at number 13
Kukai has to finish in the top five
At the halfway mark
He's sitting near the back of the field
That was 202 go he starts to make his move
It's a great result for who kind
When did the
Despite running a great race
2K still doesn't know if it'll be enough to raise his overrule School
The results come in for some of the students the Finishing Line seems as far away as ever
But who Chi has done it
Do with his written exam is just a month away
Not only half the battle
Another niggar GG
Play saxophone now
Felicia
At shooting High School Headmaster who has cold in the parents
They're also being prepared for the exams
Yeah yeah
Piyo
Ghost Hawk
Schembari
Pop NSYNC
Singapore
Which one
It's a worrying time to Louis you phase mom
She gave up her career to become a full-time cook and Coach Valdosta
Email
Hyundai Bluetooth
It's 5:30 a.m.
And the children at Pigman have to get the school spotless before the golden week holiday
Then it's a breakfast of steamed bread buns rice and boiled eggs
Synagogue Hasina
A school breaks up
Parents arrived to take the children home
Despite having been ready for nearly five hours
It looks like I'm paying will have to wait for Grandpa a while longer yet
Begin
Texas resale Pasadena
How much does a 1090
What happened
Google Play lalalalala
Holiday on the show 90 Festival
On the way
It's a time to relax
Unless you're revising with only five days until the mokes
Every minute counts for the exam students
As the week comes to an end
The festivities climax
And revision reaches Fever Pitch
Kitchen
Tucson
So will you say I'm tsukai
These marks of the last test before the real exams in a month
11 indication of what they still need to do to get into that First Choice University
Meanwhile
Trion Middle School
Lucian is sitting his marks to
He hopes that next year if all goes well
He'll be able to transfer to shooting High School
2 Days Later the shooting students are given the results
Post Office Port student who kite
Please
Beatnik
Second District student will yufei
She scored the highest Mark in the school's history
But good results in the marks don't seem to ever leave the tension
Computer Johanna
Kombucha
Zion Middle School
Lesions mock results abuso coming
Pizzahut.com
And all
Children
You Shanks dad is giving him the one thing he really wants besides exam success
Animal
Google how you doing
Can you
It's a big year for all of these children
Unfortunately we may the year of the golden pig has started well
It's also been an auspicious start to the exam students at Sheldon High School
They got through their mouth
But the greatest challenges now just a month away
Next time on Chinese School it's the real thing
How will you say do in the gaokao
The most competitive exam system in the world
To find out more about Elijah schoolchildren and Sheldon go to open to.net
Have your say about tonight's program over to sign up for our Weekly Newsletter
Busiest bbc.co.uk / BBC full
Coming up tonight another channel to see the final episode of a year in Tibet
Next